  {
    "levelName": "Strings",
    "index": "4",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"hello\"",
            "answer": "olleh"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"world\"",
            "answer": "dlrow"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"python\"",
            "answer": "nohtyp"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"ahhhhhhhh\"",
            "answer": "hhhhhhhha"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/OneStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/OneDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"abcdefg\"",
            "answer": "aceg"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"123456\"",
            "answer": "135"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"python\"",
            "answer": "pto"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"12345678\"",
            "answer": "1357"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/TwoStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/TwoDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"hello\"",
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"world\"",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"python\"",
            "answer": "1"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"zach\"",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"education\"",
            "answer": "5"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/ThreeStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/ThreeDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"radar\"",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"level\"",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"hello\"",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"rotor\"",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"Zach\"",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/FourStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/FourDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"hello world\", \"-\"",
            "answer": "hello-world"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"Python is great\", \"_\"",
            "answer": "Python_is_great"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"a b c\", \"*\"",
            "answer": "a*b*c"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"zach is cool\", \"_\"",
            "answer": "zach_is_cool"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "PuzzleInfo/FiveStartingCode.txt",
        "directions": "PuzzleInfo/FiveDirections.txt",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  }
